Guide to the Richard Foreman and Kate Manheim Papers MSS.152
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: Scripts
  - "He Was Expected Soon" annotated script., undated (Box 16, Folder 514)
  - "He Was Expected Soon" photocopy of annotated script., undated (Box 16, Folder 515)
  - "Here Comes the Boat" script, plastic ring binding. HEader: "Fred's dogs", Footer "holy moly", undated (Box 16, Folder 516)
  - "Hero Cadmus/Samuel/ (no) Samuel II". This folder includes "Hero Cadmus", part 1 of 4., undated (Box 16, Folder 517)
  - "Hero Cadmus/Samuel/(no)Samuel II". This folder includes "Samuel" part 2 of 4., undated (Box 16, Folder 518)
  - "Hero Caddmus/ Samuel/ (no) Samuel II" This folder includes "Samuel Two", part 3 of 4., undated (Box 16, Folder 519)
  - "Hero Cadmus/ Sameul/ (no) Sameul II" This folder includes "Suburbate" part 4 of 4., undated (Box 16, Folder 520)
  - "Hey script bound in clear plastic folder [with stickey binding], 1994 (Box 16, Folder 521)
  - "Holy Moly" annotated typescript, heavy cut-and-paste., undated (Box 16, Folder 522)
  - "New Holy Moly or the P[illegible]" script with annotations. Part 1 of 2., undated (Box 16, Folder 523)
  - "New Holy Moly or the P-[illegible]" script with annotations. Part 2 of 2., undated (Box 16, Folder 524)
  - "Old" [filed with Holy Moly material, after the folder "New"], undated (Box 16, Folder 525)
  - "Honor" original script., undated (Box 16, Folder 526)
  - "Hotel China" work copy., undated (Box 16, Folder 527)
  - "hcohtienla or Hotel China" string bound scripts., undated (Box 16, Folder 528)
  - "hcohtienla or Hotel China", undated (Box 16, Folder 529)
  - "Hotel for Criminals" Libretto by Richard Foreman, Music by Stanely Silverman. Work copy, includes acts 1 and 2., undated (Box 16, Folder 530)
  - "Hotel for Criminals" libretto by Richard Foreman, music by Stanley Silverman. Photocopied text of acts 1 and 2., undated (Box 16, Folder 531)
  - "Hotel for Criminals" libretto by Richard Foreman, music by Stanley Silverman. Act 1 work copy., undated (Box 16, Folder 532)
  - "Hotel for Criminals: the second part entitled The American Imagination" libretto by Richard Foreman, music by Stanley Silverman. Text photocopy., undated (Box 16, Folder 533)
  - "Hotel for Criminals" Libretto by Richard Foreman, music by Stanely Silverman. Act two annotated text., undated (Box 16, Folder 534)
  - "Hotel for Criminals" text by Richard Foreman, music by Stanley Silverman. Act two annotated text., undated (Box 16, Folder 535)
  - "Hotel for Criminals" text by Richard Foreman, music by Stanely Silverman. Act two annotated text., undated (Box 16, Folder 536)
  - "Hotel for Criminals, an Opera" Text and photographs photocopied from published book., undated (Box 16, Folder 537)
  - "Hotel for Criminals, an Opera" Text and photographs photocopied from published book., undated (Box 16, Folder 538)
  - "Hotel Fuck/Paradise Hotel" original script with annotations., undated (Box 16, Folder 539)
  - "Sexual Naivete" [Hotel Fuck/Paradise Hotel], undated (Box 16, Folder 540)
  - "Human Beings: Multiple Brains" script., undated (Box 16, Folder 541)
  - "Human Beings with Multiple Brains" script., undated (Box 16, Folder 542)
  - "Ida-Eyed" script, undated (Box 16, Folder 543)
  - "Ida Eyed" annotated script., undated (Box 16, Folder 544)
  - "Idiot:Nothing" annotated script with napkin., undated (Box 16, Folder 545)
  - "Idiot:Nothing" annotated page 1, undated (Box 16, Folder 546)
  - "Idiot B'wards" annotated script, header "Nothing", undated (Box 16, Folder 547)
  - "Idiot Savant" script. Header "Idiot:Nothing", undated (Box 17, Folder 548)
  - "Idiot Savant" script with annotated folder. Header "Idiot--Something", undated (Box 17, Folder 549)
  - "Idiot Savant" plastic spiral bound script with annotations., undated (Box 17, Folder 550)
  - "Incohere I" script dated 11 May 1994. Clear plastic binder. (Box 17, Folder 551)
  - "Incohere II" script dated 24 July 1994. Clear plastic binder. (Box 17, Folder 552)
  - "Inspirational analysis" original script, undated (Box 17, Folder 553)
  - "Inspirational Analysis" copy of original script., undated (Box 17, Folder 554)
  - "Inspirational Analysis" typescript with annotations., undated (Box 17, Folder 555)
  - "I've got the shakes" script with annotations and inserts., undated (Box 17, Folder 556)
  - "Jeweled" script with annotations, undated (Box 17, Folder 557)
  - Script page fragments. [These match those of the above folder but were not labeled as such. Paper appears to be degrading.], undated (Box 17, Folder 558)
  - "King Cowboy Rufus Rules the Universe" script dated 20 October 2003 (Box 17, Folder 559)
  - "King Cowboy Rufus" script dated 20 November 2003. (Box 17, Folder 560)
  - "King Cowboy Rufus" script dated 1 December 2003. (Box 17, Folder 561)
  - "King Cowboy Rufus" rehersal script dated 7 December 2003. (Box 17, Folder 562)
  - "King Cowboy Rufus" December rehersal script dated 10 December 2003. (Box 17, Folder 563)
  - "King Cowboy Rufus" script dated 10 December 2003. (Box 17, Folder 564)
  - "King Cowboy Rufus" script dated 10 December 2003. (Box 17, Folder 565)
  - "King Cowboy Rufus" script dated 10 December 2003. (Box 17, Folder 566)
  - "King Cowboy Rufus" script dated 19 December 2003. (Box 17, Folder 567)
  - "King Cowboy Rufus" script dated 28 December 2003., undated (Box 17, Folder 568)
  - "King Cowboy Rufus" script dated 1 January 2004 (Box 17, Folder 569)
  - "King Cowboy Rufus" script dated 1 January 2004 (Box 17, Folder 570)
  - "King Cowboy Rufus" early material, undated (Box 17, Folder 571)
  - "King Cowby Rufus" annotated script., undated (Box 17, Folder 572)
  - "King Cowboy Rufus" annotated script., undated (Box 17, Folder 573)
  - "King Cowboy Rufus"annotated script., undated (Box 17, Folder 574)
  - "King Cowboy Rufus" annotated script. Header: "Racecar", undated (Box 17, Folder 575)
  - "King Cowboy Rufus" script p. 1-21, undated (Box 17, Folder 576)
  - "King Cowboy Rufus" script pages and drawings. Also Labeled "Creative and Stone 'The World's Heart'", undated (Box 17, Folder 577)
  - "King Cowboy Rufus" annotated fragments, undated (Box 17, Folder 578)
  - "King Cowboy Rufus" annotated fragments, undated (Box 17, Folder 579)
  - "King Cowboy Rufus extra, expanded" annotated script., undated (Box 17, Folder 580)
  - "King Cowboy Rufus" miscellaneous fragments., undated (Box 17, Folder 581)
  - "King Rudolpho/Emperor" script and inserts., undated (Box 17, Folder 582)
  - "Lava Plus" script, folder labeled "Odd", undated (Box 17, Folder 583)
  - "Lava" script., undated (Box 17, Folder 584)
  - "Left Field" folder, empty. annotated., undated (Box 17, Folder 585)
  - "Life of the Bee (I've Got der Shakes)" annotated typescript, undated (Box 17, Folder 586)
  - "Lines of Vision" annotated typescript., undated (Box 17, Folder 587)
  - "Lines of Vision" script., undated (Box 17, Folder 588)
  - "Loonies" script in folder, undated (Box 17, Folder 589)
  - "Loonies" script in plastic binder, undated (Box 17, Folder 590)
  - "Loonies" annotated script, undated (Box 17, Folder 591)
  - "Lost (catastrophy)" annotated folder and script fragments., undated (Box 17, Folder 592)
  - "Love and Science" original, undated (Box 17, Folder 593)
  - "Love and Science" annotated script., undated (Box 17, Folder 594)
  - "Love and Science" script, undated (Box 17, Folder 595)
  - "Luogo + Bersaglio" English typescript., undated (Box 18, Folder 596)
  - "Luogo + Bersaglio" Englishscript bound with red string., undated (Box 18, Folder 597)
  - "Luogo + Bersaglio" annotated English script, undated (Box 18, Folder 598)
  - "Luogo + Bersagio" annotated English script., undated (Box 18, Folder 599)
  - "Luogo + Bersaglio" English working script, undated (Box 18, Folder 600)
  - "Luogo + Bersaglio" English working script with sound annotations., undated (Box 18, Folder 601)
  - "Luogo + Bersaglio" English working script, undated (Box 18, Folder 602)
  - "Luogo + Bersaglio" English working script., undated (Box 18, Folder 603)
  - "Luogo + Bersagio" Italian translation with Harry Matthews notes., undated (Box 18, Folder 604)
  - "Luogo + Bersaglio" Theater of Rome, Italian text., undated (Box 18, Folder 605)
  - "Madame Adare (A Psychoanalytical Masque)" text by Richard Foreman, music by Stanley Silverman. Annotated script, undated (Box 18, Folder 606)
  - "Madame Adare" text by Richard Foreman, music by Stanley Silverman. Annotated script bound with staples and masking tape., undated (Box 18, Folder 607)
  - "Madame Adare" by Richard Foreman and Stanley Silverman. Script photocopied from published book., undated (Box 18, Folder 608)
  - "Madness and Tranquility" original typescript, annotated. [This play was rehersed for three months but never performed.], ca. 1978-79 (Box 18, Folder 609)
  - "Madness and Tranquility (My Head was a Sledgehammer)" incomplete first draft. Photocopy with original annotations., ca. 1978-79 (Box 18, Folder 610)
  - "Madness and Tranquility (My Head was a Sledgehammer)" incomplete first draft. Photocopy with original annotations., ca 19778-79 (Box 18, Folder 611)
  - "Madness and Tranquility" annotated script., ca. 1978-79 (Box 18, Folder 612)
  - "Madness and Tranquility" dialogue and stage direction script., ca. 1978-79 (Box 18, Folder 613)
  - "Madness and Tranquility" script., ca. 1978-79 (Box 18, Folder 614)
  - "Maestro" script, undated (Box 18, Folder 615)
  - "Maestro Adds, Page 40-Storm" annotated script. part 1 of 2., undated (Box 18, Folder 616)
  - "Maestro Adds, page 40-Storm" coverpage "dismember" script. Part 2 of 2., undated (Box 18, Folder 617)
  - "Maestro" script, undated (Box 18, Folder 618)
  - "Maestro: Texas" script in clear plastic binding., undated (Box 18, Folder 619)
  - "Maria del Bosco" original annotated text., undated (Box 18, Folder 620)
  - "Maria del Bosco" annotated script with inserts., undated (Box 18, Folder 621)
  - "Maudlin Notations" original annotated typescript, undated (Box 18, Folder 622)
  - "Maudlin Notations" photocopied script, undated (Box 18, Folder 623)
  - "Maudlin Notations"photocopied script, undated (Box 18, Folder 624)
  - "Melbourn" script, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 625)
  - "Meta Reverse I" script dated 28 April 1994. Clear plastic binding. (Box 18, Folder 626)
  - "Meta Reverse II" script dated 28 April 1994. Clear plastic binding.jy (Box 18, Folder 627)
  - "The Mind King" script, undated (Box 18, Folder 628)
  - "The Mind King" annotated script, undated (Box 18, Folder 629)
  - "Miss Universal Happiness" original typescript with annotations., undated (Box 18, Folder 630)
  - "Miss Universal Happiness" typescript, typed by Kate Manheim., undated (Box 18, Folder 631)
  - "Miss Universal Happiness" annotated script., undated (Box 18, Folder 632)
  - "Miss Universal Happiness" script and press interfiled. "Produced NYC 1985" (Box 18, Folder 633)
  - Unidentified script, header "More 2", undated (Box 18, Folder 634)
  - "My Head was a Sledgehammer" annotated script. Cover pages: "1st rehersal script with blood", undated (Box 18, Folder 635)
  - "My head was a sledgehammer" annotated script, black plastic spiral binding. Cover "Music RF"., undated (Box 18, Folder 636)
  - "My head was a sledgehammer" annotated script, black plastic spiral binding., undated (Box 18, Folder 637)
  - "My head was a sledgehammer" annotated script., undated (Box 18, Folder 638)
  - "My head was a sledgehammer" script., undated (Box 18, Folder 639)
  - "My head was a sledgehammer" script., undated (Box 18, Folder 640)
  - "My head was a sledgehammer" script., undated (Box 18, Folder 641)
  - "My head was a sledgehammer", cover page "Final text". Two copies., undated (Box 18, Folder 642)
  - "My life, my death" original text by Kathy Acker., 1982 (Box 18, Folder 643)
  - "My life, my death" labeled "original". Text by Kathy Acker., 1982 (Box 18, Folder 644)
  - "My life, my death" handwritten section or addition., undated (Box 18, Folder 645)
  - "My life, my death" original French typescript, undated (Box 18, Folder 646)
  - "My life, my death" French translation fragment page 10, Leiris., undated (Box 18, Folder 647)
  - "My life, my death" French script, p. 1-19. Translated by Kate Manheim and Noel Burch., undated (Box 18, Folder 648)
  - "My life, my death" French script, p 1-60. Translated by Kate Manheim and Noel Burch., undated (Box 18, Folder 649)
  - "My life, my death" French script p. 1-10. Translated by martine Feldman., undated (Box 19, Folder 650)
  - "My life, my death" photocopy of annotated French script,unknown translator., undated (Box 19, Folder 651)
  - "Names" script dated 28 April 1994. Clear plastic binder. (Box 19, Folder 652)
  - "Newer" scro[t dated 4 September 1994. Clear, plastic binder. (Box 19, Folder 653)
  - "No Atmosphere Paris Cafe"script, header: "Supreme beings", undated (Box 19, Folder 654)
  - "No Atmosphere Catastrophe Paris Cafe" script, header: "More 2", undated (Box 19, Folder 655)
  - "No Atmosphere Catastrophy Paris Cafe" fragments., undated (Box 19, Folder 656)
  - "Nothing I" script. Clear plastic binder., undated (Box 19, Folder 657)
  - "Nothing II" annotated script with inserts. Clear plastic binder., undated (Box 19, Folder 658)
  - "Now that Communism is Dead" annotated script. Header: "Music stuff 2", undated (Box 19, Folder 659)
  - undated (Box 19, Folder 660)
  - "Occult City of Paris". Two different kinds of typed pages interfiled. Grouped and labeled by Richard Foreman., undated (Box 19, Folder 661)
  - "OP/RA: an isomorphic representation of the gradual dismembering from wihtin of Western art in which a new unity that of consciounness itself emerges." Text by Richard Foreman, Music by Stanley Silverman. Annotated typescript., undated (Box 19, Folder 662)
  - " Out of the body travel" annotated script., undated (Box 19, Folder 663)
  - "Out of the body travel" annotated script., undated (Box 19, Folder 664)
  - "Pain(t)" script., undated (Box 19, Folder 665)
  - "Pain(t)" script, undated (Box 19, Folder 666)
  - "Pancake People (Gods are pounding my head)", 2004 (Box 19, Folder 667)
  - "Pandering to the Masses" annotated script with cut-and-paste., undated (Box 19, Folder 668)
  - "Pandering to the masses: A Misrepresentation" script and New York Times review., 1975 (Box 19, Folder 669)
  - "Pandering to the masses" work copy, undated (Box 19, Folder 670)
  - "Pandering to the masses" work copy, lighting and sound direction., undated (Box 19, Folder 671)
  - "Pandering to the masses" annotated script with lighting directions., undated (Box 19, Folder 672)
  - "Pandering to the masses" artservices typescript., undated (Box 19, Folder 673)
  - "Pandering to the masses: A misrepresentation", undated (Box 19, Folder 674)
  - "Panic" annotated script, undated (Box 19, Folder 675)
  - "Paradise" script., undated (Box 19, Folder 676)
  - "Particle Theory" script., undated (Box 19, Folder 678)
  - "Pearls for Pigs" annotated script., undated (Box 19, Folder 679)
  - "Pearls for Pigs" script dated 4 April 1997., undated (Box 19, Folder 680)
  - "Pearls for Pigs" annotated script., undated (Box 19, Folder 681)
  - "Pearls for Pigs" French script. Translated by Anne Berelowitch. Published by Theatre de Gennevilliers, Paris., undated (Box 19, Folder 682)
  - "Penguin Touquet" version C dated 23 October 1980. (Box 19, Folder 683)
  - "Penquin Touquet" script dated 16 January 1981 (Box 19, Folder 684)
  - "Penguin Touquet" script dated 16 January 1981. (Box 19, Folder 685)
  - "Penguin Touquet (x)2(x)Indian(x)" annotated script., undated (Box 19, Folder 686)
  - "Penguin Touquet" script., undated (Box 19, Folder 687)
  - "Permanent Brain Damage (uncut original) script. Footer: "cabtalk3", undated (Box 19, Folder 688)
  - "Permaneent Brain Damage" script. Cover also indicates "Long". Script footer: "cabtalk3", undated (Box 19, Folder 689)
  - "Permanent Brain Damage" script dated 4 November 1996., undated (Box 19, Folder 690)
  - "Permanent Brain Damage" annotated script. Cover "PDB R-3", undated (Box 19, Folder 691)
  - "Permanent Brain Damage" annotated script., undated (Box 19, Folder 692)
  - "Permanent Brain Damage" fragments. Folder labeled "xtra", undated (Box 19, Folder 693)
  - "Permanent Brain Damage" annotated sound effects script., undated (Box 19, Folder 694)
  - "Planet Earth (Dreams)" annotated script., undated (Box 19, Folder 695)
  - "Plus ???" annotated script in clear plastic binding., undated (Box 19, Folder 696)
  - "Point A" annotated script in clear plastic binding., undated (Box 19, Folder 697)
  - "Point 2" script in clear plastic binding., undated (Box 19, Folder 698)
  - "Race Car" annotated script and folders., undated (Box 20, Folder 699)
  - "Race Car" annotated script., undated (Box 20, Folder 700)
  - "Rays/New Play/ Eddie Goes and Language" part 1 of 2, "Rays", undated (Box 20, Folder 701)
  - "Rays/New Play/Eddie Goes and Language" part 2 of 2, undated (Box 20, Folder 702)
  - "Real Magic in New York" an opera, text by Richard Foreman, music by Steve Dickman.Original typescript., 1970 (Box 20, Folder 703)
  - "Real Magic in New York" an Opera. Text., 1970 (Box 20, Folder 704)
  - "Real Magic in New York" an Opera. Annotated text., 1970 (Box 20, Folder 705)
  - "Real Magic in New York: An A'Capella Opera" Text by Richard Foreman, Music by Stephan Dickman. Script and score., 1970 (Box 20, Folder 706)
  - "Real Magic in New York: An A'Capella Opera" Text by Richard Foreman, Music by Stephan Dickman. Script and score for Scene 4., 1970 (Box 20, Folder 707)
  - "The Remarkable Cabin Cruiser: Depth" annotated script., undated (Box 20, Folder 708)
  - "Remarkable Cabin Cruiser (Depth)" annotated script., undated (Box 20, Folder 709)
  - "Rhoda in Potatoland" annotated script., undated (Box 20, Folder 710)
  - "Rhoda in Potatoland" typescript. Folder labeled "76-PL-344", undated (Box 20, Folder 711)
  - "Rhoda in Potatoland" photocopy of typescript in folder 711., undated (Box 20, Folder 712)
  - "Rhoda in Potatoland" photocopy of script., undated (Box 20, Folder 713)
  - "Rhoda in Potatoland" annotated scripts, includes sound effect annotations., undated (Box 20, Folder 714)
  - "Rhoda in Potatoland" annotated script, includes sound effects annotations., undated (Box 20, Folder 715)
  - "Rhoda in Potatoland" annotated script., undated (Box 20, Folder 716)
  - "Rhoda in Potatoland" photocopy of annotated script., undated (Box 20, Folder 717)
  - "Rhoda in Potatoland" script and press in folder labeled "Foreman, R. 76-Pl-344", undated (Box 20, Folder 718)
  - "Rhoda in Potatoland" French script with annotations., undated (Box 20, Folder 719)
  - Miscellaneous page included amidst "Rhoda in Potatoland" materials., undated (Box 20, Folder 720)
  - "Rhoda Returning" copy of annotated script., undated (Box 20, Folder 721)
  - "The Rise and Fall of the City of Mahogonny" annotated text., undated (Box 20, Folder 722)
  - "The Rise and Fall of the City of Mahogonny" piano and vocal score., undated (Box 20, Folder 723)
  - "Roly Poly" text., undated (Box 20, Folder 724)
  - "Roly Poly in China + Holy Moly + Catastrophy" annotated script with inserts, undated (Box 20, Folder 725)
  - "Sadness" script., undated (Box 20, Folder 726)
  - "Sadness" photocopied script., undated (Box 20, Folder 727)
  - "Sadness" annotated script., undated (Box 20, Folder 728)
  - "Sadness" annotated script., undated (Box 20, Folder 729)
  - "Sailor Boy" annotated script., undated (Box 20, Folder 730)
  - "Salzburg" text. Header: "Berl-slz", undated (Box 20, Folder 731)
  - "Samuel's Major Problems" script., undated (Box 20, Folder 732)
  - "Samuel's Major Problems" script, undated (Box 20, Folder 733)
  - "Samuel's Major Problems" bound script., undated (Box 20, Folder 734)
  - "Samuel's Major Problems" bound annotated script., undated (Box 20, Folder 735)
  - "Samuel's Major Problems" bound lighting script., undated (Box 20, Folder 736)
  - "Samuel's Major Problems"unbound lighting script., undated (Box 20, Folder 737)
  - "Seance-Shorts", "Making contact with sources (A seance)" annotated typescript., undated (Box 20, Folder 738)
  - "Seance-Shorts", "The End of a Beautiful Friendship" typescript., undated (Box 20, Folder 739)
  - "Seance-Shorts" untitled typescript, first line "I prefer to be the world's smartest person"., undated (Box 20, Folder 740)
  - "Seance-Shorts" untitled typescript, first line: "Everything about me, all aspects of my life...", undated (Box 20, Folder 741)
  - "Seattle:Sweet:New Play" annotated text in clear plastic folder., undated (Box 20, Folder 742)
  - "Seattle: Buddah P'ting: Texas" annotated text with inserts., undated (Box 20, Folder 743)
  - "Secret Performances" script in clear plastic binder., undated (Box 20, Folder 744)
  - "Shunzo Kuku" script, undated (Box 20, Folder 745)
  - "Sledgehammer" annotated script., undated (Box 20, Folder 746)
  - "Sledgehammer" script in clear plastic binding., undated (Box 20, Folder 747)
  - "Slice" annotated script., undated (Box 21, Folder 748)
  - "Slight" text, undated (Box 21, Folder 749)
  - "Songs" annotated script., undated (Box 21, Folder 750)
  - "Songs" script p. 1-33, undated (Box 21, Folder 751)
  - "Sophia=(wisdom)" script, undated (Box 21, Folder 752)
  - "Sophia=(wisdom) part III: The Cliffs" script, undated (Box 21, Folder 753)
  - "Sophia=(wisdom) part III: The Cliffs" annotated script, undated (Box 21, Folder 754)
  - "Sophia=(wisdom) part III: The Cliffs" annotated script, includes sound effects and lighting annotations., undated (Box 21, Folder 755)
  - "Sophia=(wisdom) part III: The Cliffs" annotated script, includes sound effects and lighting annotations., undated (Box 21, Folder 756)
  - "Space" annotated script., undated (Box 21, Folder 757)
  - "Space City" annotated script., undated (Box 21, Folder 758)
  - Stage Fright (many lines, repeated by others--stasis with music)" script., undated (Box 21, Folder 759)
  - "Stage Fright: Motel" annotated script, undated (Box 21, Folder 760)
  - "Storm, Seattle" photocopy of annotated script., undated (Box 21, Folder 761)
  - "Strong Medicine" original typescript with annotations., undated (Box 21, Folder 762)
  - "Strong Medicine" annotated script with inserts, including budget notations., undated (Box 21, Folder 763)
  - "Strong Medicine" script titled "Richard Foreman Film Project, Initial Shooting Script", 1978 (Box 21, Folder 764)
  - "Strong Medicine" annotated script., undated (Box 21, Folder 765)
  - "Strong Medicine" annotated script., undated (Box 21, Folder 766)
  - "Strong Medicine" annotated script., undated (Box 21, Folder 767)
  - "Strong Medicine" annotated script, undated (Box 21, Folder 768)
  - "Strong Medicine", undated (Box 21, Folder 769)
  - "Strong Medicine" annotated screenplay. [still has staples], undated (Box 21, Folder 770)
  - "Strong Medicine" Kate's annotated script., undated (Box 21, Folder 771)
  - "Strong Medicine" annotated script, undated (Box 21, Folder 772)
  - "Strong Medicine" photocopy of annotated script., undated (Box 21, Folder 773)
  - "Strong Medicine" annotated script, undated (Box 21, Folder 774)
  - "Strong Medicine" annotated script, undated (Box 21, Folder 775)
  - "Strong Medicine" annotated script. Removed from binder in folder 777., undated (Box 21, Folder 776)
  - "Strong Medicine" first French translation, typescript., undated (Box 21, Folder 778)
  - "Strong Medicine" French translation, annotated typescript., undated (Box 21, Folder 779)
  - "Strong Medicine" script fragments, undated (Box 21, Folder 780)
  - "Strong Medicine" script fragment with notecard inserts., undated (Box 21, Folder 781)
  - "Strong Medicine" script fragments., undated (Box 21, Folder 782)
  - "Suppose" text, undated (Box 21, Folder 783)
  - "Suppose" annotated script., undated (Box 21, Folder 784)
  - "Suppose 2" script, undated (Box 21, Folder 785)